Facing Life is a drama film directed by Jon Perry.
After communication ceases, Kevin breaks out of prison to find his
lifelong girlfriend, but is met with some unfortunate news.
Gloria, played by Ann Mahoney.
Kevin, played by Adam Masnyk.
Detective Sullivan, played by Timothy P Stanton.
Katie, played by Emily Camparone.
Dada (transl.
Father) is a 2023 Indian Tamil-language coming-of-age romantic
comedy drama film written and directed by Ganesh K.
Babu, in his directorial debut.
Produced by Olympia Movies, the film stars Kavin and
Aparna Das in the lead roles, alongside K.
Bhagyaraj, Aishwariyaa Bhaskaran and VTV Ganesh.
The story follows a college student who embraces fatherhood, providing care and love
to his child while facing the challenges of life as a single father.
The film has music composed by Jen Martin, editing by K.
Ezhil Arasu and cinematography handled by Kathiresh Alagesan.
Dada was released theatrically on 10 February 2023 to positive reviews.